A Guide to the Fairfax County Public Library System Map Collection, 1894-1977
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Fairfax County Public Library System Map Collection 1943-1994
The Library of Virginia
5672-5688, 5873, 5886, 5892, 5896, 5900, 5901
8 map folders
Fairfax County Public Library System
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia from the Fairfax County Public Library System in 2006.
Historical Information
The Fairfax County Public Library System donated 183 printed maps to the Library of Virginia in 2006.
Scope and Content
The Fairfax County Public Library System is comprised of 183 printed maps printed between 1943 and 1994. Most are color lithographs that were published by local northern Virginia governments, state and federal government agencies and printed by private and public entities. The maps cover such topics as industrial zones, planning districts, subdivisions, townships, bicycle trails, streets, Washington Area Metro System, coastal surveys, Bouguer Gravity, total intensity magnetic map, solid waste refuse collection, retail and commercial development, residential development, Northern Virginia, Fairfax County, American Revolutionary War, voting precincts, industrial development, sub census tracts, public parks, sanitary sewer lines, freeway system, watersheds, water distribution lines, natural gas distribution lines, historic sites, magisterial districts, public schools, aeronautics, congressional districts, fishing maps, trails, and city and county boundaries.
Several businesses, government agencies are represented also: Fairfax County Industrial Development Authority, Fairfax County Planning Commission, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, Department of Commerce - Bureau of the Census, U.S. Government Printing Office, Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, Alexandria Drafting Company, U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, Williams and Heinz Map Corporation, Fairfax County Communications Division, Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation, Economic and Industrial Development Committee of Fairfax County, (Virginia) State Corporation Division of Aeronautics, City of Fairfax, Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Conservation, Economic Development Division of Mining, Minerals and Malcolm Blue Print and Supply Company, Richmond (City) Chamber of Commerce, Waynesboro-East Augusta Chamber of Commerce, Staunton-Augusta County Chamber of Commerce, Richmond City Planning Commission, Richmond Metropolitan Authority, Rand McNally and Co., Champion Map Corporation, Arlington County, United States Forest Service, Bureau of the Census, and United States Department of Commerce. These are filed in Cabinet 29, Drawer 12.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession number.
Contents List
- Accession 5673, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Rockingham County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5674, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Rockbridge County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5675, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Cumberland County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5676, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Isle of Wight County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5677, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Bath County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5678, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Sussex County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5679, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Washington County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5680, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Madison County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5681, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Wythe County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1949. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5682, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Wythe County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1949. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5683, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Smyth County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1949. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5684, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Dinwiddie County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5685, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Richmond County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1944. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5686, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Spotsylvania County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1949. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5687, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map, Goochland County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1948. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5688, Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, Virginia Polytechnic University, "Land Classification Map King and Queen County, Virginia", Scale of miles,1960. (Folder 1)
- Accession 5873, Fairfax County Industrial Development Authority, "Fairfax County Virginia Prepared by Fairfax County Industrial Development Authority", 43 x 38.5 inches, Scale 1:20,000, 1965. (Box 2)
- Accession 5873A, Fairfax County Planning Commission, "Fairfax County Virginia Prepared by the Fairfax County Planning Commission", 42.5 x 37.75 inches, Scale 1:22,000,1953. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873B, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax: Corridor Alternatives Springfield Bypass and Extension", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale 1: 15,000,1979. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873C, Fairfax Planning Commission, "Map of Fairfax County Virginia Compiled in the Office of Carpenter and Cobbs Certified Land Surveyors", 31.75 x 51.5 inches, Scale 1:3000,1962. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873D, Fairfax County Planning Division, Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Planning Division, 55.5 x 48.75inches, Scale 1: 3,000,1966. (Folder 2)
- . Accession 5873E,Division of Planning Fairfax County, Virginia, "Lower Potomac Planning District; A Summary of the Plan Adopted by the Board of Supervisors October 25, 1967", 34 x 24 inches, Scale 1:24,00,1967. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873F, Division of Mapping, "Fairfax County Upper Potomac Planning District Community Facilities Plan", 34.25 x 23.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000, 1969. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873G, Division of Mapping, "Fairfax County, Virginia "Upper Potomac Planning District Policies Plan", 34.25 x 23.5 inches, Scale 1: 24,000, 1969. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873H, Division of Planning, "Fairfax County, Virginia, Bull Run Planning District", 38.5 x 25.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000, 1969. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873I, Division of Planning, "Fairfax County, Virginia, "Bull Run Planning District Comprehensive Plan Phase 1 - 1975", 38.5 x 25.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1969. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873J, Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, "1970 North Carolina County Subdivisions, Townships and Places", Scale 43 x 19 inches, Scale 1 inch equals 10 miles,1970. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873K, Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, "Bicycle Paths in the Washington Area", 38 x 45 inches, Scales varies, 1977. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873L, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Regional Map System Adopted March 1, 1968 by the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority", 33.5 x 43.25 inches, Scale not given,1974. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873M, U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, "Chesapeake Bay Wolf Trap to Smith Point. U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey", 33.5 x 40.75 inches, Scale 1:80,000,1943. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873N, Stanley S. Johnson and Palmer C. Sweet, "Bouguer Gravity and Total Intensity Magnetic Map Fluvanna County", 30.5 x 35.5 inches, Scale 1:62,500,1969. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873O, Fairfax County Communications Division, "Commonwealth of Virginia, County of Fairfax, County-wide Trails Plan", 43.5 x 38 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873P, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia, County of Fairfax, Solid Waste Refuse Collection", 43.75 x 38 inches, Scale in feet,1978. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873Q, Fairfax County Communications Division, "County of Fairfax, Commonwealth of Virginia fire and Rescue Department Assignment Box System", 43.75 x 38 inches, Scale in feet and miles,1984. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873R, Fairfax County Planning Commission, "Fairfax County Virginia Proposed Plan of Industrial Development and Employment Centers", 43.75 x 39.25 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873S, Fairfax County Planning Commission, "Fairfax County Virginia Proposed General Plan of Retail and Commercial Development", 43.75 x 39.25 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873T,[Fairfax County Planning Commission], "Fairfax County Proposed Plan of Residential Development", 44 x 39.25 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873U, Fairfax County Planning Commission, "Fairfax County Virginia Proposed General Plan of Land Utilization", 44 x 39.25 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873V,[Fairfax County] Communications, Large Area Mapping, "Fairfax County Area IV Plan: Springfield, Rose Hill, Mt. Vernon, Lower Potomac Planning Districts: Adopted by the Board of Supervisors July 28, 1975, Amended through November 1, 1983, 42 x 40 inches, Scale in feet,1983. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873W,[Fairfax County] Communications, Large Area Mapping, Fairfax County Area III Plan: Pohick Planning District: Area III Plan Map is shown on Three Separate Maps: Adopted by the Board of Supervisors, June 30, 1975, amended through November 1, 1983, 40 x 40 inches, Scale in feet,1983. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873X, [Fairfax County] Communications, Large Area Mapping, Fairfax County Area II Plan: McLean, Vienna, Fairfax Planning Districts: Adopted by the Board of Supervisors August 25, 1975, Amended through November 1, 1983, 42 x 40 inches, Scale in feet,1983. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873Y,[Fairfax County] Communications, Large Area Mapping, "Fairfax County Area I Plan: Jefferson, Baileys, Annandale, Lincolnia, Planning Districts Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 16, 1975, amended through November 1, 1983", 36 x 36 inches, Scale in feet,1983. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873Z, Fairfax County Communications, Large Area Mapping, "Fairfax County Area III Plan: Bull Run District: Area III Plan is shown on Three Separate Maps: Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975, amended through November 1, 1983", 40 x 36 inches, Scale in feet,1983. (Folder 2)
- Accession 5873AA, Commonwealth of Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, "Virginia: Independence Bicentennial Commission American Revolutionary War Map, 1774-1783", 22 x 40.5 inches, Scale in feet,1976. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873BB, Fairfax County Communications Division Large Area Mapping Branch, "Commonwealth of Virginia: County of Fairfax: Voting Precincts for Congressional Elections", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873CC, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Comprehensive Plan Commercial and Industrial Development", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet,1977. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873DD, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Sub Census Tracts", 42.5 x 37 inches, Scale in feet,1963. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873EE, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Sub Census Tracts", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet,1968. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873FF, Fairfax County Mapping Division, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Sub Census Tracts", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale in feet,1969. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873GG, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Public Parks", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet,1977. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873HH, Economic and Industrial Development of Fairfax County, "Fairfax County Virginia Sanitary Sewer Lines", 32.25 x 29.5 inches, Scale in feet,1962. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873II, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Proposed Freeway System", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in feet,1960. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873JJ, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Major Watersheds", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1960. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873KK, Economic and Industrial Development Committee of Fairfax County, "Fairfax County Virginia Water Distribution Lines", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1962. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873LL, Economic and Industrial Development Committee of Fairfax County, "Fairfax County Virginia Natural Gas Distribution Lines", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1962. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873MM, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Industrial and Land Use and Zoning Plan", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1960. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873NN, Fairfax County Division, "Fairfax County Inventory of Historic Sites", 28 x 24.5 inches, Scale in feet,1976. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873OO, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "County of Fairfax Sub Census Tracts", 28 x 24.5 inches, Scale in feet,1977. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873PP, [Fairfax County] Planning Division, "County of Fairfax Planning Division", 28 x 24.5 inches, Scale in feet,1969. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873QQ, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Magisterial District", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1960. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873RR, Fairfax County Planning Division, Fairfax County Virginia Land Use", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1960. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873SS, "Fairfax County Planning Division, Fairfax County Public Schools", 32.5 x 29.5 inches, Scale in miles,1962. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873TT, "Commonwealth of Virginia, Virginia Aeronautical Chart, 1970-1971", 26 x 57.75 inches, Scale in nautical and statute miles,1971. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873UU, [City of Fairfax], "City of Fairfax Private Street", 17.75 x 22.25 inches, Scale in feet,[1997]. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873VV, [City of Fairfax], "City of Fairfax Private Street", 15.75 x 22.25 inches, Scale in feet,No date. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873WW, Commonwealth of Virginia, "Glen Allen Quadrangle Virginia Geology", 22.5 x 18 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1981. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873XX, Mervin G. Bartholomew, "Geology of the Blacksburg Quadrangle, Virginia", 23 x 19 inches, 1:24,000,1979. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873YY, Bureau of the Census, U.S. Department of Commerce, "Congressional Districts for the 92nd Congress, Includes Redistricting Actions to August 1, 1970", 25.25 x 38 inches, Scale 1:5,000,000,1970. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5873ZZ, Malcolm Blue Print and Supply Company, "Map of the Roanoke Valley Metropolitan Area, Virginia", 23.25 x 33.5 inches, Scale in feet and miles,1981. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5886, Eugene M. Scheel, "Culpeper County, Commonwealth of Virginia", 34 x 43 inches, Scale in statute miles, Located in Map Reading Room, Filed under 755.383 1975 Copy 1,Revised January 1970. (Folder Filed under 755.383 1975 Copy 1)
- Accession 5886A, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "County of Fairfax Voting Precincts", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet,1979. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886B, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "County of Fairfax Watersheds", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale in feet,1974. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886C, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "County of Fairfax Industrial Zoning", 41.75 x 36.5, Scale in feet,1972. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886D, "US. Geological Survey with Bureau of Public Roads and State Highway Departments, United States of America, Federal Aid Highways, the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways, the Federal Primary Highway System, and the U.S. Numbered Highway System, Highway Status as of March 1, 1965", 36.75 x 59.75, Scale 1:3,168,000,Not dated. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886E, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Sub Census Tracts",1961. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886F, Fairfax County Communications Division, "County of Fairfax, Voting Precincts for Congressional Elections - Even years, Legislative Elections - Odd Years", 42 x 36.75, Scale in feet,1980. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886G, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, "Fairfax County Area III Plan, Land Use Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975, Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning District", 46 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1975. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886H, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, "Fairfax County Area III Plan, Land Use Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975. Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning Districts", 46 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1975. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886I, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, "Fairfax County Area III Plan, Land Use, Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors August 25, 1975, McLean, Vienna and Fairfax Planning Districts", 37.25 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1975. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886J, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, "Fairfax County Area III Plan, Land Use, Transportation, and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975, Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning Districts", 46 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1975. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886K, E. L. Lowry and Susan Williams, "Commonwealth of Virginia 1967 Traffic Flow Map, Interstate Arterial and Primary Routes, Annual Average 24 Hour Traffic, Year Ending Dec. 31, 1967", 16 x 35.25 inches, Scale in traffic scale,1967. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886L, Michael T. Lukert and Christopher R. Halladay, "Geology of the Massies Corner Quadrangle Virginia", 28 x 81 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1980. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886M, Stanley S. Johnson, "Gravity Map of Virginia, Simple Bouguer Anomaly", 27.5 x 58.5 inches, Scale 1:500,000,1977. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886N, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Lake Anna", 22 x 34.75 inches, Scale 1:24,000,No date. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886O, Alexandria Drafting Company, "James River Fishing Map from Richmond to Norfolk Includes Chickahominy River", 33 x 20.5 inches, Scale 1:80,000,1981. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886P, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Prepared by Fairfax County Planning Division", 42.75 x 38.75 inches, Scale in feet,1936. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886Q, Fairfax County Economic Development Authority, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax Sanitary Sewer Facilities", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale 1:48,000,1946. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886R,[Fairfax] Division of Mapping of the Office of Comprehensive Planning, "Area III Preliminary Plan Map January 1975, Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning Districts", 36.75 x 49.25 inches, Scale in feet, 1932. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886S, Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, "Fairfax County Area 1 Plan Land use, Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 16, 1975, Annandale, Bailey's, Jefferson and Lincolnia Planning Districts", 28.5 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet,1955. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886T, Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning, "Fairfax County Area IV Plan Land Use and Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 28, 1975, Lower Potomac, Mount Vernon, Rose Hill and Springfield Planning Districts", 45 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1933. (Folder 3)
- Accession 5886U, Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning, "Fairfax County Area III Plan Land Use Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975, Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning Districts", 76 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1976. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886V, Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning, "Fairfax County Area III Plan Land Use, Transportation and Public Facilities Adopted by the Board of Supervisors June 30, 1975, Upper Potomac, Bull Run and Pohick Planning Districts", 44.25 x 39.75 inches, Scale in feet,1976. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886W, Fairfax County Industrial Authority, "Commonwealth of Virginia, County of Fairfax, Utilities Map", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale in feet,1970. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886X, United States Forest Service, "Appalachian Trail: Mt. Rogers National Recreation Area, George Washington and Jefferson National Forests", 12 x 27.75 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1993. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886Y, United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service Southern Region, "North Half Appalachia Trail Wythe Ranger District, Jefferson National Forest, Virginia; Map No. Two", 18.75 x 28 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1936. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5886Z, Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, Inc., "Appalachian Trail in Northern Virginia Potomac River to Snickers Gap, Map Seven", 24 x 10.5 inches, Scale 1:50,000,1994. (Folder 4)
- Accession 5892, Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, "Appalachian Trail Across Maryland Including the Catoctin Trail Maps 5 and 6", 33 x 24 inches, Scale 1:62,500,(W 77°45’--W 77°30’/N 39°45’--N 39°30’),1992. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892A, Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, "Appalachian Trail in Northern Virginia South Half Snickers Gap to Chester Gap", 31 x 22 inches, Scale 1:62,500,1993. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892B, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Potomac River Fishing Map from Hains Point to Smith Point", 20.5 x 33 inches, Scale 1:80,000,(W 77°28’--W 75°52’/N 38°54’--N 37°45’),1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892C, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Rappahannock River Fishing Map Includes Piankatank River, Corrotoman River, Piscataway Creek, Totuskey Creek, Cat Point Creek, Occupacia Creek, Mount Landing Creek", 22 x 35 inches, Scale 1:80,000,1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892D, Alexandria Drafting Company, "York River Fishing Map", 33 x 19.75 inches, Scale 1:80,000, (W 77°16’--W 76°12’/N 37°49’--N 37°05’),1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892E, Appalachian Trail Conference, "Appalachian Trail Map No. 5 Pedlar Ranger District, George Washington National Forest", 19 x 28.25 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1985. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892F, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Chincoteague-Assateague Fishing and Recreation Map", 21 x 27.25 inches, Scale [ca. 1:26,500],1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892G, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Lower Chesapeake Bay Fishing Map from Smith Point to Lynnhaven Inlet", 20.5 x 33 inches, Scale 1:80,000,(W 76°24’--W 75°37’/N 37°54’--N 36°55’),1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892H, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Virginia Beach Fishing Map", 20.5 x 33 inches, Scale 1:80,000,(W 76°24’--W 75°30’/N 37°08’--N 36°32’),1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892I, Williamsburg Area Chamber of Commerce, "Map of Williamsburg, James City County and York County, Virginia", 17 x 27.75 inches, Scale 1:43,000,1978. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892J, Williamsburg James City County Chamber of Commerce, "Map of Williamsburg and James City County, Va", 17 x 21.5 inches, Scale ca. 1:29,000,[1974]. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892K, Ken Brown, "Champion Map of Danville Virginia Including Detailed Maps of Chatham and Pittsylvania County", 19.75 x 26 inches, Scale in miles,1974. (Folder 5)